Hello and welcome to our English listening practice.
مرحبا بكم في تدريبنا على الاستماع للغة الإنجليزية.
How are you today?
كيف حالك اليوم؟
Is your listening getting better step by step?
هل استماعك يتحسن خطوة بخطوة؟
I hope so.
آمل ذلك.
Today's listening practice will help you
تدريب الاستماع اليوم سيساعدك
even more than before.
أكثر من أي وقت مضى.
Try to imagine yourself in this situation.
حاول أن تتخيل نفسك في هذا الموقف.
For example, what would you do if you
على سبيل المثال، ماذا ستفعل لو أنك
were at a supermarket and couldn't find your
كنا في سوبرماركت ولم أجد لك
favorite snack?
وجبة خفيفة مفضلة؟
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
This is a great way to practice
هذه طريقة رائعة للممارسة
for real life situations.
للمواقف الواقعية.
After this lesson, please share with me in the comments
بعد هذا الدرس، يرجى مشاركتها معي في التعليقات
how you feel after practicing with us.
كيف تشعر بعد التدريب معنا.
In today's lesson
في درس اليوم
we will practice useful English words and phrases
سنمارس كلمات وعبارات إنجليزية مفيدة
for the restaurant.
للمطعم.
Have you ever gone to a restaurant
هل سبق وأن ذهبت إلى مطعم
in another country and felt nervous
في بلد آخر وشعرت بالتوتر
about speaking English?
عن التحدث بالإنجليزية؟
Or maybe you didn't understand what the waiter said.
أو ربما لم تفهم ما قاله النادل.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
In this video, you will learn how to order food
في هذا الفيديو، ستتعلم كيفية طلب الطعام
and speak politely in English at a restaurant.
وتتحدث بأدب بالإنجليزية في مطعم.
I will speak slowly and clearly
سأتحدث ببطء ووضوح
so you can follow easily.
لذا يمكنك المتابعة بسهولة.
You can listen carefully and repeat after me if you want.
يمكنك الاستماع جيدا وتكرار القصة خلفي إذا أردت.
This will help both your listening and speaking skills.
هذا سيساعد مهاراتك في الاستماع والتحدث.
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟
Let's go.
هيا بنا.